Hello everyone. My name is Harukawa Koizumi, aka Oharu.
Yes, so today.
I answered one, oh, oh, 100 questions!
This is a project that I've been getting requests for.
I'm going to answer 100 questions!
I have never answered 100 questions before!
So this is going to be a little bit long video.
I hope you all enjoy it!
Well, I have recruited on Instagram!
Thank you!
Now, I'd like to answer them right away!
I'll just go ahead and poof!
Wow! Wow, we got 5,000!
5000 for 100 questions!
Thank you!
Well, I'll answer a few excerpts!
I'll try to make it clear, you know.
I feel like I should write something positive or something.
I feel like I'm in trouble.
Positive letters are very primitive.
It's a little bit old-fashioned.
I'll get some paper, paper.
I have to write it down.
I don't know how many I've counted.
Whenever I select a question box, I always carefully select from the beginning.
I'm always very selective from the beginning.
But this time, I didn't have much time.
I'm going to answer a hundred questions.
I will answer 100 questions.
Okay, here we go!
Oharu, what is your favorite part of your makeup?What is Oharu-chan's speciality in makeup?
This is the first one.
Oharu-chan's makeup obsession
Recently, I try to use slightly darker eye shadow.
I like mature makeup.
Here's what I'm doing today.
A little bit around the eyes.
Dusky pink eyeshadow?
I like to use eye shadow like this.
I like to use dark eye shadow.
I like to use dark eye shadow to give a mature impression.
I like to use it to give a mature impression.
This kind of color eye shadow.
I like to put this around the corner of the eyes.
But if that's all you do, it's a little too dark, so I like to use some kind of lame to cover it up.
I like to use some kind of lame to cover it up.
I also like to use a dark lip color like this.
I've also been using black mascara lately.
I also like to lighten my eyebrows by one or two tones.
As for my eyebrows...
I learned this from an eyebrow make-up artist.
Visee Instant Eyebrow Color No. BR2. I love this color because it's so cute!
I also use Lilimu's In the Mirror Eye Palette No. 03 Winter Gray as eyeshadow.
I like to use a color that looks like a glaze.
I like to use a color that looks a little bit like a glaze, but it's not too harsh.
I like to use a color that's a bit harsh.
But the lamé can make it look a little fake.
I'm into mature and cute makeup.
Thank you very much for your question. Thanks for the question.
Let's continue.
What is your favorite thing about Julia?Can you tell me what you like about Julia?
Of course I do.
What I like about you, Julia...
Her graceful dance moves.
And the way she moves forward and backward.
And also...
Since Haru and Julia performed together on stage, they started talking seriously about their work.
I wonder if there are things that she tells only to me.
Julia often complimented me on my singing. She often asked me how I could hit the high notes.
She often compliments me on my singing.
I'm a person who likes singing a lot.
I'm very happy when Julia praises my singing.
Like, when she listens to me sing.
Also...
Bangs? There are a lot of things I really like about her, like her bangs... and her dryness... and her dryness.
There are a lot of things I really like about him. Next year, I hope we can go out for dinner again.
Third one...
Third, have you read the DM? I do! I read all your DMs and replies to your stories, so I read all your mentions when I can.
If I have time, I check the mentions on my instagram.
I'm sorry, but since the latter half of December, I can't open my instagram outside the house because of the communication limitation.
So I don't update my Insta as much as I used to, but I have Wi-Fi at home, so when I have Wi-Fi, I look at it.
I'm the kind of person who looks for Wi-Fi all the time, so lately I've become a Wi-Fi addict.
How's your strength training going? I've been slacking off on my strength training lately.
I'm going to find out how many positive numbers I need to write to reach 100.
I'll find out how many positive letters it takes to make 100.
Why did you choose this picture for your Insta icon? I think it's the one with the braids.
I used to have a different one, but it's just so tiny.
You can see everyone's icons like this, right? When you look at them, you see a bright face or something.
I thought it was cute to see a bright face or a face that looks like "Wow! I think that's why I chose that icon.
And then, do you like Eechi? I love Eech-chan. I worked with Eech-chan on a TV show called Music Globe the other night.
She's so cute and every time I see her, you know...She was incredibly cute, and every time, you know...
Whenever we took pictures, Ichi would ask if she could sit next to me and take a picture with me, and she was so cute.
I hope I can go on a date with Eechi next year.
What was your most memorable concert in 2022?
Well, Makuhari Messe was one, but I was most impressed with Girls Land. I'm sure I've talked about Makuhari in various places.
This year, Girls Land was held at Zeppahaneda, and I was so happy that nearly 4,000 girls came to see us.
So I was really happy that there were so many more girls than at the previous Girls' Land.
The girls were so sparkly and pretty, and they came with lots of makeup and fashion.
Of course, the boys also cut their hair when they come to the show, and I think they are very particular about it.
I'm so happy that everyone does so many things before coming to see us.
I think Girls Land was a live that will go down in history, and I want to do my best to make the girls like us even more.
Are there any idols other than Studan that you are close with?
I personally really like Spaga, and I watch their music videos without fail.
I also like Katorena from AKB48.
She told me that she also watches my YouTube channel, so I really hope we can have a dinner sometime.
I'd be really happy if we could have dinner sometime.
Please take a look.
What is your favorite hairstyle of a girl?
I'm going to the next concert with that haircut!
I like the half-twin hairstyle that Hiyori wore on Jikketsu because it's so cute!
I think the half-twin is really cute and blends in with the hair that's down.
Is there a song you want to play on the guitar now?
I'd like to play Kaleido Proud Festa by Unison Sky Garden.
This song has a lot of chords that are great for practicing on the guitar, and it's a great song to practice on.
It's a great song to practice while playing.
Also, "Tokise no Star" is also a good practice song.
Next year, I'd like to show some of Oharu's guitar practice.
I'm a total beginner, so I can't do it...
Yes, Kaleidoproud Festa and Star are good songs to practice.
If you could change the color of the members, what would it be?
I usually play warm colors, so...I usually work with warm colors.
I like to wear green or something like this in my clothes, and I don't mean to be rude to Hiyori, but I like to wear darker colors.
I like to wear darker colors because they give me a sense of restraint.
So I'd like to wear green or blue, not pastels.
I always want to wear blue when I wear kimono.
I'd like to wear purple and other cool colors.
Oharu-chan's top 3 favorite songs in Jikkou
Let's see, my top 3 favorite songs of Jikkou
Recently, there was a change in the ranking.
Then, the top 3!
I'll meet you at Shibuya Tsumemaw.
I like it
Yes, I like them.
When they sing or dance... it's so much fun... I like it.
No.1
Tomorrow's strongest theory
I like them a lot these days.
I like them a lot because I hear them a lot and see them live a lot.
If I say I like it, it's like it's a standard song.
When people say they like a song, they tend to choose a minor song, like me.
But lately I've been wearing my favorites.
It's so much fun to dance.
I see.
What is your favorite Disney character?
Well...
Not Stella Lou.
I like Gelatoni.
He's a character from the Disney scene.
She's a cat.
I like Gelatoni.I like gelatoni.
I wonder if there are 10 kinds.
There it is! Cachuccinos!
I've got some cleaning to do.
I like gelatoni.
Let's answer this question in Geratoni-style!
What song from the show did you think you could sing?
What song did you think you sang well?
Well, this video will probably be released at the beginning of the new year.
I think I sang "Cider in July" in the last year before last.
I liked that July Cider a lot.
I'm personally wondering if the video will be uploaded on YouTube...
After Julia sang the last part of the song, I asked her if I could see her again.
It's not Julia who sings the "ochi-chabi" part.
After Hiyori and Aki-chan sang the chorus, I said, "Will I see you again?
Then Julia sang the 3rd chorus.
I thought it was one of the live videos of that July Cider concert.
I thought it was one of those live performances.
What kind of ramen have you been into lately?
The ramen I've been into recently.
There's a Sapporo ramen restaurant called Kita no Daichi.
Sapporo Miso Ramen? Miso Butter Ramen was delicious!
It's pretty high on my list.
How often do you eat ramen?
I eat ramen about 6 times a week.
If I combine ramen, soba and udon...
I think I eat ramen about 7 or 8 times a week.
I eat standing-only buckwheat noodles and regular cup ramen, etc.
I think that's about how often I eat ramen.
What is ozoni like in the Koizumi household?
The Koizumi family's ozoni is rather light.Koizumi family's ozoni is rather light and simple.
It's just regular family zoni with daikon radish and carrots.
There's nothing special about the taste.
I think it's pretty light.
It doesn't have any miso in it or anything.
It doesn't have any miso or anything, and it's not too clear.
I think it's a rather orthodox ozoni.
You can put as much rice cake as you like.
I want to know the origin of the name.
The origin of the name?
Well, the origin of the name...
Originally, it was a name that would be given when spring was born.
It was either Haru or Haru or Haru or Haru as it is now.
I heard that it is better to be named Haru or Haru-ka than Haru or Haru-ka when you are born.
I heard that it was better to be named Haruka than Haru or Haru when I was born.
Is this the origin of the name?
If it's true... it smells like spring...
I hope that's the origin of the name.
I'm sorry, it's not what I expected.
I like the fringe, but do you plan to have it done?
I like bangs like this for now.
They're not see-through, but they're a little thinner.
I went to a hairdresser.
I think I like bangs like this because it's the most relaxed.
I've recently become addicted to Tokisen. Thank you! Please let me know what kind of songs you like.
I would recommend "hop step jump love," which I performed at the Jikkuri the other day.
The choreography has a lot of jumps in it, so please remember it!
Call the members? What? Call the members? I wonder if they will answer.
What? Who should I call?
But I've been called by Kanamin once when she was playing YouTube. I wonder if she's busy right now.
I'm a little scared and nervous! I'm getting a stomach ache. I'll call Kanamin.What a little scary nervousness! I'm getting a stomach ache. I'll call Kanamin.
Let me show you the speaker.
I'm scared. Maybe she won't answer.
Doesn't look like she'll answer.
I don't think she'll answer. Let's call Hiyori-chan.
I wonder if Hiyori is there now.
Scary, scary.
I'm scared, I'm scared My stomach hurts
My stomach hurts
I'll call Hiyori-chan
I'm scared
I'm so nervous I'm so nervous I'm so nervous I'm so nervous
Yes!
I quit.
It was a train.
Well, maybe everyone is busy.
I think I can get out.
Yuri, you were on the train.
It's not working.
Maybe everyone's busy right now.
Everyone's busy right now.
That doesn't sound good.
I'll try again later.
It's been cold lately. How do I get out of bed in the morning? I'm pretty sure I'm falling asleep twice.
It's so cold these days.
I don't get out of the futon very often.
I'm the kind of person who always gets out of the futon after thinking I'm going to work hard.
I don't get out from under the covers.
But...Uh, but...
I'm going to get up and get out.
That's the only orthodox answer I can give you.
I can't do it anymore. I can't do it.
I'm sorry I got a little too upset about this.
I'm sorry I couldn't give you a good answer.
I want to know what made you decide to become an idol.
What made you decide to become an idol?
I don't know... I don't know...
I didn't have a clear reason.
It's not like I originally raised my hand, but...
It's not a raise of the hand, but...
Well...
We were looking for people who wanted to be in the group, and we held auditions.
Originally we were a group called Tokimeki Advertising Club, but we created a new group called Tokimeki Advertising Club, and we continued after that.
So I didn't start idolizing because I really wanted to be an idol or because I auditioned for it.
But I think it was a very good decision for me to become an idol.
If I had another life, if I had this chance to become an idol, I probably would have become an idol without hesitation.
I'm very glad that I'm here now even though I didn't have the chance to become an idol.
Yes, I am.
What is the one thing you can't lose to anyone?
I think I have a pretty good memory. I can remember the birthdays of everyone in STAPLER.
I can remember the birthdays of my family, friends, and relatives.
And then there is the mentality of steel.
Do you prefer Bolano or Apino? I prefer Apino.
What is the hardest song to dance to in the special selection? The hardest song is "hop step jump love" which we are currently performing as a new song.
The reason why it's the hardest is because the jump in that song doesn't have an auxiliary run.
hop step jump love is not a song where you prepare for each jump.
So each jump has a clear landing.
And the endless jumps are always tough.It was very strenuous and my muscles ached a lot.
If I were to go somewhere by myself, I would like to go to Ishikawa Prefecture.
If I were going somewhere alone, I would like to go to Ishikawa to eat delicious fish.
My favorite way to eat rice cake is with soybean flour or sugar and soy sauce.
I like to eat mochi with soy sauce and sugar.
I'd like to try the same thing again.
I'd like to add a spicy element to my ramen, even if I'm eating salt ramen.
I'm the kind of person who likes spicy food, so I definitely want to add spicy ingredients.
I want to add vegetables, kimchi, eggs, green onions.
I want to add green onions, that's about it!
I'd like to put some mayonnaise on it so that I can eat it with rice.
Oh man, I'm running out of batteries.
I think the hair that leaks at live shows is overwhelmingly fried hair.
I think the hair that's fried, not pulled down, is the one that leaks the most.
What is your favorite mendou other than ramen? I love soba by far.
I'll give you 70 more answers. Is there any part of the other members you would like to sing?
Do you want to sing any of the other members' parts?
I'd like to sing "I want to let you know" from "Hop Step Jump Love" and "I want to let you know".
If you were a producer yourself, what kind of live show would you like to put on?
Well, I'd like to sing "Sweet Sweet Days" and "July Cider" in the set.
and July Cider... and maybe a lot of sad songs like that.
I'm sure they'll be a lot of standards and sad songs like that, but not sad songs.
I like that kind of worldview, so I'd like to do a live show with that kind of worldview.
What is your favorite ramen?
What is my favorite ramen?
Well, lately I like spicy ramen the best.
Do you have a favorite YouTuber?
I think Sky Peace is the one I watch the most.
I've been using a lipstick lately called Opieux.
Opew's tint.
Yeah, it's OK.Yes, OK.
I'll continue.
What is the first song that comes to mind when you think of a song to play during a battle of time?
What is the first song that comes to mind?
Springed
How did you decide on the members' colors?
The members' colors were decided by
The boss at the office decided it for us.
He said, "You should be pink.
I was yellow at first.
But he decided for me.
I think pink is now well established.
What kind of girl is your type?
I want to be your type of girl.
What is your type of girl?
A girl like Kanami.
There's something about her that makes me want to help her
I want to help her out.
I want to help her.
I'd like to do the project we were working on earlier
I'd like to do it again.
Um...
I was told by a fan
I was told by a fan...
I think it's about time.
I'll call him.
Will he pick up?
Maybe not. I don't know.
Hello?
I got it! Hello?
What is it? Hello?What's up? Hello?
Where are you?
I'm there, recording.
Oh, my God! Are you okay?
I'm totally fine. Why?
Well, you know, I'm on YouTube right now.
They told me to call you, so I did.
So I did.
Did you get it?
Just now.
What? It's recording.
I called Hiyori earlier.
She's on the move.
I couldn't use it at all.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm Angelea.
This is Julia.
I couldn't get out. I was two minutes late.
Oh, really? Good luck with the recording.
Thank you.
I tried singing. I tried singing.
I tried singing. Yeah, I'll try my best.
Okay, so you're the publicist in front of the camera.
In front of the camera, or rather, to the publicity people who are watching this...
What would you like to say?
Um, this video.
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel and like and comment.
please subscribe, like and comment!
Please do.
So, that was Angelea!So that was Angelea!
Thank you. Good luck.
Sorry.
Okay, bye-bye.
Okay, bye.
It's safe to call you.
I made it.
I just told you, Hiyori.
I tried to call her, but she was on the move.
I was able to make a call, so...
It will be added here, yes.
Is there anything you want to do before your birthday?
Cleaning.
I haven't been able to get my clothes on the floor at all.
I'd like to do a step-by-step of my clothes.
Is there anything you would like OHARUSHI to do?
Hmmm...
But of course I would be very happy if you could make me a fan or something.
What else would you like?
Hmmm...
I don't know...
Well, I'm glad that you send me a lot of love.
I'm a little heavy on the love, so I think a little bit of love is just right.
I'd like to know your routine for tired days.
Tired day?
But some kind of tired day.
Hmmm...
What do you do on a tired day?
I eat a lot of spicy ramen noodles.
I want something stimulating, and it's a day when I'm tired.
I just recently got to know Tokisen and would like to go to a live concert.I just recently discovered Tokisen and would like to go to a live concert.
Thank you very much.
What is a live concert like?
Well, I'm not able to do voice now.
I used to do a lot of live performances with my voice.
But now...
I don't know if it's really appropriate to say this, but...
But now, I'd like people to see me as if I were an artist performing live.
But we, the promoters, the fans, are called "promoters.
I think the charm of a live concert is the sense of unity with the fans and the promoters.
I can't get them to call out to me, but I can get a lot of applause and fenlight.
We can't get them to call out to us, but we can get them to cheer us on with applause and fenlight.
It's like a space where you can enjoy our songs together.
And what I think is the charm of a live concert?
The charm of music?
I think the charm of a live concert is to have everyone enjoy the music.
TOKISEN's music has a variety of songs.
There are so many variations of songs.
I think you can enjoy the melodies of the songs and the expressions of the members
I hope you will enjoy the melody of the songs and the expressions of the members.
I wonder if I'm singing well? The charm of the live performance
Fast-talking...wait....
Do you think you're good at fast-talking with your current glibness?
Are you good at fast-talking?
Snow plowman, please repeat three times while plowing.
Here we go!
Snow plow, snow plow, snow plow, snow plow, snow plow...
What? Don't want to go?
Do you have a question for us? Well, please write down your favorite food in the comments!
What would you like to be if you were born again? I'd like to be a dog.
What song are you listening to the most these days? I'm listening to the song "Snow Song" the most.What song are you listening to the most these days? I'm listening to a song called "Snow Song" the most.
This is a song written by Takumi Yoshida of Saji, and I listen to it a lot.
Favorite color? Black Favorite event? Christmas and Halloween.
I like Christmas. I like going to see the illumination with my best friend during Christmas season.
What would you like to do outside of being an idol? What would you like to do outside of being an idol?
I'm not really good at anything, but I'd like to be a caviar attendant or a flight attendant.
Do you have a favorite costume of an idol other than Jikkensen? The Jikkens? Do you have a favorite non-Time War idol costume?
I really like Momoguro's Christmas costume with the plover pattern.
What is your favorite brand of clothes? Recently, I like Public Tokyo and Beams.
Beams, Snaidel, Lily Brown, Chico, and Heather.
Chico, Heather, and I don't know, Zara.
Dazzlin, Mauzy, and Sly.
What's your latest craze? My boom is crunchy plums.
Also, at the Kikuri-Kuri, the staff gave us some delicious pickled plums and we heard a recipe for eating them in ochazuke (rice with green tea).
I answered your question earlier. My favorite Sanrio character is Batsumaru, but I've been loving Pochakko lately, too.
I'd like to try a new hair color... I'd like to do that... a little blonde mesh on my bangs.
I'd like to try it. My favorite drink is a good unsweetened afternoon tea.
My favorite snack is blanc choux. My favorite song in the battle of time is "Seishun Heartshake".
I like girls who wear light-colored clothes.
I also look up light-colored girls on Instagram and wear brands I think are cute, but I prefer the clothes of girls who wear beige or white.
If you were to change colors for one day during the battle, what color would you prefer?
Let's dare to pick one favorite thing about each member, Ms. Hanami.
Hanami-san, the eyes that disappear when she smiles.
Julia-san's clear and beautiful high tone.
Ms. Autumn's smile when she says something unexpected.
Hiyori-san, who makes me laugh by saying something out of the ordinary when I'm not expecting it.
I've never been to a live performance of "Toki-Sen," but I'd like to go.
I'm a beginner, but I'd be happy to come.
I like to say that I'm going to work hard, I like to say that I'm not going to give up a hundred times, I like to say "thank you", I like to say "thank you".
I like "thank you," "I love you," "I'll take good care of you," and "I'll take good care of you.I like "thank you," "I love you," "I'll take good care of you," and "I'll take good care of you.
I'm also happy when I'm told I'm doing my best.
I'm happy to be called "Harchan", "Ha", "Haru", "Haru"... I'm happy to be called by any other name.
I'd like to know your personal color.
I like this color a lot, but I'm not a Bourbe, I think I'm an Autumn at home person.
I think that's the color I'm most comfortable with.
I was good at Japanese, English and music, but if I did it now I'd probably be good at PE too.
I don't get much anymore... just something really nice... like a barber or something... but I don't get it if I'm just a normal person.
I don't get it from my mom or anything... what do you like to eat for Osechi (New Year's Eve)?
OharaYukiI can't drive on the road because I can't even drive normally.
I don't eat New Year's soba every year because I forget what it's like.
I also like mantle baboons and mandrills.
If you had a time machine, what would you rather do in the past or the future?
What is the first thing you do when you get home?
Tell me the order in which you eat Pinot.
I like pinot.
I'll eat this first.
And after that, I'll eat like this.
I eat this one last.
Like this.
What song would you like to play next?
I would like to play the song "Absolute Happiness" by Nana Mizuki.
by Nana Mizuki.
Where would you go on a date with me?
What a cute question!
Well, I don't know!
Yes, that's right.
If you can come up with 5 more questions with positive answers, you're good to go!
That's it!
25 in the afternoon, so 25 more questions25 p.m., 25 questions later
If you won the lottery, what would you do?
If I won the lottery
I'd like to buy a facial cleaner for starters.
Oh, and lighting.
I'd like to buy a facial cleaner.
Also, I'd like to buy lots of clothes.
And I want to buy lots of cosmetics.
I think that's about it.
Also, I want to increase my stock of cup noodles.
I want to know what kind of body care and skin care products you use!
For skin care, I've been using Muji lately.
For body care, I tend to use Jill Stuart and the like.
What did you eat this morning?
I didn't eat breakfast, but I had a beef bowl for breakfast and lunch at a bar-bunch.
Is it OK to say that you can enjoy Raging Spirits up to the point where you can feel the floating sensation?
It's OK.
I can enjoy Raging Spirits.
It's just for a moment.
The other day, I went to Yomiuriland for the illumination.
At the illumination...
It was like Flying Pirates.
There was this kind of thing.
There was this one that rotated really slowly.
The one at Yomiuriland.
I thought it was absolutely impossible.
This is the lipstick I'm using now.
This is Rimmel's Marshmallow Rock Lipstick No. 22.
It's a pretty natural bluish pink.
I want to hear about the dream you had with the advertising guy.
We're pretty much in love.I'm pretty much in love with her.
Well, I'm not a person who usually has many friends.
That's why the advertising department members are in the same classroom.
I would ask him to come over for a minute, and he would come out of the classroom.
And he came out of the classroom.
and we walk down the hallway alone and talk.
That kind of lovey-dovey dream.
If I were to get a dog, would it be a toy poodle?
But I also like Chihuahuas.
Maybe a toy poodle, a chihuahua, or a Pomeranian.
But after seeing Leo, I think Maltese are cute too.
But I also think that Leo is cute.
Favorite idol group
My favorite idol group Super Girls
I like Equal Love.
Since when do you laugh like that?
There is a story behind this.
When I was in elementary school, there was a girl whom I had a crush on who I thought was cute.
I was in elementary school, and there was a girl whom I admired and thought was cute.
But she was laughing quite loudly.
I guess she wanted to start from the beginning.
She was imitating the way she laughed, and I could feel her laugh.
What hairstyle do you think suits each member?
Kanami's braids, which she's been doing recently.
Julia has a half up-do.
Hito-chan has a ponytail.
Aki-chan has a bun.
Two buns.
Hiyore has two buns.
Do you have a favorite scent? Do you have a favorite perfume?
There were a lot of questions about this one.There were a lot of questions about this one.
Perfume.
It's a white freesia mist.
It's like a body mist, like this Fernanda one.
There are a lot of Fernanda's body mists.
I think they both have a floral scent that is refreshing and fluffy.
Do you have a regular menu item that you order when you go to Starbucks?
When I go to Starbucks, I might order a lot of caramel rolled art.
What is your favorite cup ramen?
I love spicy ramen noodles in a bag.
Also, I love kamja noodles.
I've introduced it on Ramen TV, so please check it out!
Who takes the lead in making the set list for live performances, the members or the staff?
This is completely up to the staff.
We often don't know the set until rehearsals start!
The thing I want to try the most right now is dragon fruit!
And two more! Se-no, ji!
What song do you really want to sing at the side show?
I haven't decided on anything yet.
The best melody of my life
Do you eat popcorn in a movie theater? I don't eat popcorn because of the noise.
I do eat popcorn.
I love the caramel popcorn at United Cinemas.
What are your top 3 favorite songs by Unison Square Gunden?
I can't choose anymore.
I can't choose, but I tend to choose
I can't choose...
Carade Proud Festa
After taking into account the fact that I really can't choose
Mixed Juice is right.Mixed Juice is right.
I really can't choose, and that's something I really want you to take into account.
Of all the things I'd like to see taken into account, I guess I'd have to say Prologue for the 101st time.
I like those three songs.
I really wish you would take into account the fact that I can't choose!
Can you recommend a good night's sleep?
Goods for a good night's sleep
I wonder if it would be a good night's sleep toy.
This one.
You are sleeping with this baby in your arms
I'm sleeping with this baby in my arms.
Ambingoods
Can you give me some tips on how to lose weight?
I'm stressed out.
Dieting tips?
I don't know. I don't diet.
I don't know, but if I try to diet too hard...
I think I'll gain weight or eat because of stress.
I think I eat because I'm stressed.
I think it's okay to eat when you want to.
When I want to eat
I eat about 4 meals a day.
I think it's fine.
Do you want to wear a dress or a kimono for your wedding?
Definitely a dress.
Would you go to a ramen restaurant alone?
I would totally go.
I can go to a ramen restaurant by myself.
I sometimes go to a ramen restaurant alone after going to the dentist.
What is your favorite Momokura song?What do you like best among Momokura's songs?
I really like White Wind.
I also like Sora no Curtain.
I have a new boyfriend.
When should I tell my parents?
I feel like my parents will find out and I'll be fine.
But it's not like that.
Whenever you think it's okay to tell them.
It's fine.
It's something new.
Is this the last question?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
This is the last one.
If you want to try something new...
What would you like to try?
I'm thinking next year, maybe this year.
I've already been wanting to do swimming this year.
I haven't been able to swim for a long time.
I can't swim because I can't swim now.
I want to swim.
I also want to keep my room clean.
I would like to keep my room clean.
Okay, so...
I was able to answer the 100 questions surprisingly quickly.
Okay, what did you think?
As Jillia just told me.
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel.
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
See you again in the next video!
Bye bye!Bye-bye.
I'd like to call someone.
I don't know if he'll answer.
I've got a few minutes.
Good night.
If she doesn't answer, if she doesn't answer, I don't know.
Hello?
Hitori?
What is it? What are you doing?
Cleaning up. Sorry.
You know, I did a YouTube project where I answered 100 questions.
And one of the fans asked me to call a member, so I did.
I was really surprised.
I thought something was wrong. Hiyori was in the middle of a long, hard trip and she was unavailable.
I'm actually cleaning up my room.
Yes, so can I have your name for a second?
Hi everyone, I'm Hitoka Sakai, Hito-chan.
Hitoka.
Well, only Julia and Hitoka were able to get out together, but now...
Really? Yes, Julia, two minutes before recording.
I see... I see... I see...
I'm cleaning up with my sister, and I hear the laundry.
I'm sorry. Thank you for coming out of nowhere.
Not at all. Not at all. I thought something was wrong.
No, it's okay. Nothing's wrong. It's peaceful.
Good.
Hito-chan, can you say something to the people watching this video?
When is this going up?
I don't know. Maybe after the new year? The beginning of the year?
Yeah, maybe after the new year.
Hello everyone, are you enjoying Moal's youtube?Hello everyone, are you enjoying Moal's youtube?
No, I'm not.
HITO-chan, HITO-chan is here.
Um...
Yes, yes.
Have you cleaned up your rooms?
How are you doing?
I am working very, very hard on cleaning up my room right now.
I will do my best in 2023, Sakai.
I will do my best again in 2023.
Please, everyone, continue to love Hitoka and Hachitaro!
Please continue to love Hitoka and Hachitaro.
I look forward to working with you.
Sorry, thanks, and good luck!
I'll do my best!
Bye-bye, see you tomorrow!
Bye, bye, bye.
Oh, that's funny, I'll call you too, Jaaki!
I wonder if she'll get it. I don't know.
Maybe a little bit. I don't know.
If it doesn't come out, that's it.
If it doesn't come out, it's all right.
Oh, Aki-chan! Aki-chan!
What's wrong, Aki-chan?
What did you do? I just came home. I found a salad like sashimi, so I tried it.
Is it good? It was delicious.
I finished it. Did you try answering 100 questions for the YouTube project?
I'm filming it now... and there was a question asking me to call a member... so I did.
So I called them... and only Aki-chan, Julia and Hidaka were able to answer...
Hiyori was on the move and couldn't use it.
It was a really good question.That was a really good question. Good job.
Well, thank you very much for your time.
Well, Happy New Year. Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye bye, Harichan.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Okay, bye.
So Aki-chan left, too!
I'm so happy!
It's funny that only Hiyori and Nami didn't make it.
Well, it was fun... so here's a little extra... did you guys enjoy it?
Bye bye!